<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>g00g1y5p4's Blog</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on g00g1y5p4's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><copyright>Copyright © 2018-{year} Akash Thota. All Rights Reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 07:34:48 +0830</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/about/</guid><description>Still learning weights ^_~ come again and check for checkpoints!</description></item><item><title>Vehicle Accident Detection Using FPGA</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/vehicleaccidentdetectionusingfpga/</link><pubDate>Fri, 31 Dec 2021 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/vehicleaccidentdetectionusingfpga/</guid><description>Introduction Have you seen my previous post? If yes, I know you will definitely come here to see my new post.. 😌. what if your answer is No? Then you will definitely come here next time🥲.
What&amp;rsquo;s new this time🙄?&amp;hellip; Vehicle Accident detection using FPGA 😮‍💨.
Ew? FPGA😦? What&amp;rsquo;s that? Field Programmable Gate Arrays (FPGAs) are semiconductor devices that are based around a matrix of configurable logic blocks (CLBs) connected via programmable interconnects.</description></item><item><title>Driver Drowsiness Detection</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/driverdrowsinessdetection/</link><pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/driverdrowsinessdetection/</guid><description>Hi guys,How are you? I hope you guys are fine and missing my blogs so much.. Hah!!
This time I coming with a new topic mostly based on Image processing and ComputerVision technologies. Its sounds little bit different than previous blog, isn&amp;rsquo;t it? In this blog, we address a drowsy driver alert system that has been developed using such a technique in which the Video Stream Processing (VSP) is analyzed by eye blink concept through an Eye Aspect Ratio (EAR) and Euclidean distance of the eye.</description></item><item><title>Image Restoration Using GAN's Part-1</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/imagrestorationusinggans_1/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/imagrestorationusinggans_1/</guid><description>What is GAN&amp;rsquo;s? Generative Adversarial Networks GAN&amp;rsquo;s are one of the most interesting ideas in computer science today. Two models are trained simultaneously by an adversarial process. A generator learns to create images that look real, while a discriminator learns to tell real images apart from fakes. Case: I have read that, in most of the cases Doctors may face issues while they are making decisions over CT scanned Images because of Gaussian Noise and making electronic Noise (unwanted disturbance in a signal which is reflected in output).</description></item><item><title>Image Restoration Using GAN's Part-2</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/imagerestorationusinggans_2/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Sep 2020 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/imagerestorationusinggans_2/</guid><description>Lets continue the part-1 ^_^ ;).., We already know that what GAN&amp;rsquo;s are and why they are used. Well, not really. GANs belong to implicit learning methods. In explicit learning models, the model learns its weights directly from the data. whereas in implicit learning, the model learns without the data directly passing through the network. so it is reinforcement learning? Not really Hah..,!
As of now,we already discussed that GAN&amp;rsquo;s have two model, and two models are trained simultaneously by an adversarial process.</description></item><item><title>2048 with Python</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/2048withpython/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Apr 2020 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/2048withpython/</guid><description>Introduction Hey mates😊. How are you? Hope you all begin well. Do you know 2048 game? Yeah! Of course, everyone knew that. Ok then, Let me create it on my own 🥲.
Why I&amp;rsquo;m doing this GameBoard? Actually, One of my seniors in my college asked me to do this for their exam. That senior need to submit this GameBoard code which is written in python to get selected for InterView in OffCampus placement.</description></item><item><title>A Simple Video Call App with python Sockets</title><link>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/simplevideocallapp/</link><pubDate>Mon, 20 Jan 2020 07:34:48 +0830</pubDate><guid>https://g00g1y5p4.github.io/posts/simplevideocallapp/</guid><description>Introduction Hey mates😊. How are you? Hope you all are begin good.By the way, This is my first blog. Did you know my name 🥱? Well, I am Akash.
Why we are here? To make some fun? 😕! No, But we&amp;rsquo;re here to learn something new in a funny way. Funny while learning😒? Yeah!.,
By the way, What&amp;rsquo;s the new thing? Guess? 🤔🤔.. How to copy some code from StackOverflow easily using python?</description></item></channel></rss>